[
  { "id": 51, "question": "der Mann", "answer": "man" },
  { "id": 52, "question": "die Frau", "answer": "woman" },
  { "id": 53, "question": "das Kind", "answer": "child" },
  { "id": 54, "question": "der Junge", "answer": "boy" },
  { "id": 55, "question": "das Mädchen", "answer": "girl" },
  { "id": 56, "question": "die Eltern", "answer": "parents" },
  { "id": 57, "question": "der Vater", "answer": "father" },
  { "id": 58, "question": "die Mutter", "answer": "mother" },
  { "id": 59, "question": "der Sohn", "answer": "son" },
  { "id": 60, "question": "die Tochter", "answer": "daughter" },
  { "id": 61, "question": "der Bruder", "answer": "brother" },
  { "id": 62, "question": "die Schwester", "answer": "sister" },
  { "id": 63, "question": "der Großvater / Opa", "answer": "grandfather" },
  { "id": 64, "question": "die Großmutter / Oma", "answer": "grandmother" },
  { "id": 65, "question": "der Onkel", "answer": "uncle" },
  { "id": 66, "question": "die Tante", "answer": "aunt" },
  { "id": 67, "question": "der Cousin", "answer": "cousin (male)" },
  { "id": 68, "question": "die Cousine", "answer": "cousin (female)" },
  { "id": 69, "question": "der Freund", "answer": "friend (male) / boyfriend" },
  {
    "id": 70,
    "question": "die Freundin",
    "answer": "friend (female) / girlfriend"
  },
  { "id": 71, "question": "der Nachbar", "answer": "neighbor (male)" },
  { "id": 72, "question": "die Nachbarin", "answer": "neighbor (female)" },
  { "id": 73, "question": "der Mensch", "answer": "person / human" },
  { "id": 74, "question": "die Leute", "answer": "people" },
  { "id": 75, "question": "der Name", "answer": "name" },
  { "id": 76, "question": "der Vorname", "answer": "first name" },
  { "id": 77, "question": "der Nachname", "answer": "last name" },
  { "id": 78, "question": "das Alter", "answer": "age" },
  { "id": 79, "question": "der Geburtstag", "answer": "birthday" },
  { "id": 80, "question": "der Ort", "answer": "place" },
  { "id": 81, "question": "die Adresse", "answer": "address" },
  { "id": 82, "question": "die Straße", "answer": "street" },
  { "id": 83, "question": "die Stadt", "answer": "city" },
  { "id": 84, "question": "das Land", "answer": "country" },
  { "id": 85, "question": "der Staat", "answer": "state" },
  { "id": 86, "question": "der Arzt", "answer": "doctor (male)" },
  { "id": 87, "question": "die Ärztin", "answer": "doctor (female)" },
  { "id": 88, "question": "der Lehrer", "answer": "teacher (male)" },
  { "id": 89, "question": "die Lehrerin", "answer": "teacher (female)" },
  {
    "id": 90,
    "question": "der Student / die Studentin",
    "answer": "student (m/f)"
  }
]
